PSG is a club that has been growing for ten, eleven years,
it has been growing a lot,
it has a lot of ambition and a lot of desire to continue growing,
it has a lot of room for growth,
it has a lot of power to be able to do so.
I think that today it is one of the biggest clubs in the world
and there is not further to go, it is developing even more and getting bigger.
I think that today it has nothing to envy from thebig and historic clubs.
Winning the Champions League is complicated
because it is a competition where the best are playing,
because any detail, any mistake can knock you out of
a competition, competing against such great clubs and teams.
I think we have the team to try to win it.
I think we are very excited
and we are very eager to achieve it,
but we have to be calm,
because as I say, it is difficult to win the Champions League.
The best team doesn't always win
and you have to be aware of all the details and make a great team,
because in the end the strong teams are the ones that achieve their goals.
And we are on the way
and we are looking to make the team even stronger.
Well, Di María, Ney, I already know them from the National Team
and Ney in the past. At Barcelona we played together.
Kylian, I didn't know him on or off the field.
And well, little by little we are getting to know each other much better
and above all getting to know each other on the field
to see how we feel comfortable with each other.
And obviously it is very nice to be on the field with the best.
I was lucky enough to do it for a long time at Barcelona,
to have the good fortune to always play with the best,
and now it's my turn to do it at Paris as well.
So I'm happy and I'm looking forward to continuing doing this.
It's a very special stadium because of the way the people live it,
how they live the matches, the way they are
always singing for the whole 90 minutes.
I had already experienced it when I came here as a rival,
when I had to come many times with Barcelona.
And well, now I have it every weekend, every week.
The truth is that it is very nice.
You can hear them because they do not stop for a minute singing continuously.
The explosion of a goal, it’s a closed stadium where everything reverberates.